When I 25 f was younger maybe around ten to
twelve f I would used to do what every child
would when they grew up and ride bikes around the
neighborhood. I don't know what possessed my mind to do
this but there was a point in time where I
would ride around, stop in front of people's mailboxes, open
them, rip their mail in half, close the box and
speed off. I would do it to multiple boxes in
different parts of the neighborhood. I never got caught and
it's not that I did it much maybe about two
to three days back to back. Eventually I got the
sense that it was wrong and completely stopped but I
really don't know what would have possessed me to do
that in the first place. I just hoped that I
didn't rip up anything too important like bills or a
special letter. I definitely know better now since years have
passed but seeing this page made me randomly think of
this so I decided to leave it here and.